[
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_GatherAllies",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 58,
  "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_GatherAllies_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_03",
  "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_10 || 99_MSQ_56",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_GatherAllies_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_title",
  "Description": "99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetWiseman",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 58,
  "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetWiseman_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Grace_04",
  "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetWiseman_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_title",
  "Description": "99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateRefuge",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 58,
  "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateRefuge_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_04",
  "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateRefuge_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_title",
  "Description": "99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_InspireAllies",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 58,
  "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_InspireAllies_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_04a",
  "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_InspireAllies_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_title",
  "Description": "99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetEmpress",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 59,
  "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetEmpress_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Empress_01",
  "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_05",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetEmpress_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_title",
  "Description": "99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_AscendPeak",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 59,
  "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_AscendPeak_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Empress_01a",
  "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_06",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_AscendPeak_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_title",
  "Description": "99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateIncense",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 59,
  "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateIncense_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_05a",
  "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateIncense_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_title",
  "Description": "99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 59,
  "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Liang_01",
  "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title",
  "Description": "99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_ReuniteFamily",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_ReuniteFamily_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Grace_08a",
  "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_09",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_ReuniteFamily_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_title",
  "Description": "99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_StealBoat",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_StealBoat_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Grace_09",
  "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_10",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_09",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_StealBoat_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_title",
  "Description": "99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightEmpress",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightEmpress_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_08",
  "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_11",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_10",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightEmpress_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_title",
  "Description": "99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_DeliverPoem",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_DeliverPoem_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Yash_03",
  "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_12",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_11",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_DeliverPoem_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_title",
  "Description": "99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_complete"
 }
]